Beatrice Olofsson digital artist



"Beatrice is very competent and has broad knowledge of online and digital media. She is innovative, quick and responsible.

I can warmly recommend her."

- Jenny Gustafsson,

Project manager Go'kväll SVT

Contact

T. +46 76 832 04 01

M. beatriceolofs@gmail.com linkedin.com/beatriceolofs

beatriceolofs.netlify.app

Profile

I am a creative woman and experienced in designing a variety of digital content. I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Digital Media production and I have plenty of experience after my one year working for SVT. I am looking for a position where I can apply my knowledge and that allows me to grow as a creator.

Experience

PRODUCER & EDITOR

SVT / STORYN BAKOM 5 2022

 Producer of childrens program Storyn Bakom, responsible for animation, editing and sound.

PRODUCER & EDITOR

SVT / SEXY HANDS [2022

- Producer and editor of content for social media and DUO-app.

ONLINE EDITOR & COMMUNITY MANAGER

SVT ∫ 2022

- Identify, edit and publish content for SVTs social media and web, mainly Go'kväll and SVT Recept.

VICE INFORMATION COMMITTEE

UMEÅS MEDIE- & SYSTEMVETARFÖRENING ∫ 2019 - 2020

- Creator of digital content, responsible for social media and website design.

ARTIST

2013 - ONGOING

- Freelance artist of digital art.

Education

DIGITAL MEDIA PRODUCTION

UMEÅ UNIVERSITET [2018 - 2021

ART PROGRAM

MIDGÅRDSSKOLAN [2014 - 2017

Oualities

- Adobe Suite
- HTML (Bootstrap) & CSS
- Unity

- Aseprite
- Maya
- CMS (Escenic)

Nominiees

PRIX EUROPA 2022

2022 DIGITAL MEDIA PROJECTS

- Sexy Hands - Dating School

PRIX ITALIA 2022

2022 WEB INTERACTIVE MEDIA

- Sexy Hands - Dating School

* If interested, reference is provided.